Guide to the Robert T. Clausen papers, [ca. 1930-1980]
Clausen, Robert T. papers, [ca. 1930-1980]
- Series VIII. Wiegand Herbarium
  - Botanical Records of Kathy Krathwohl - Wiegand Herbarium, 1970s (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Series IX. Records
  - Protected Plants of New York State A (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Protected Plants of New York State B (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Protected Plants of New York State C (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Fire Ecology (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Cornell University Official Business (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Cornell University Press (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Drawing (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Ecology (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Education (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Evolution (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - General (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Greenhouse A (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Greenhouse B (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Pollination (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Publishers (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Random Numbers (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Records (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Sampling (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Records - 1958, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Records - 1966, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Records - 1967, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Records - 1969, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Records - 1970, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Records - 1971, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Records - 1971-5, 1971-5 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Records - 1965, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Records - 1976, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Records - 1978, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Sampling 2 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Science - Societies (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Speciation (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Species (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Trips (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Statistics (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Trip - New York and Washington (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Letters, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Graphtopetalum (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Graphtopetalum craiaii (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mexican Cordilleran Plateau (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Sedum - Texas (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Crassula (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - American Fern Society (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Bailey Hortorium (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Biology (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - High School Biology (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Botany Agenda (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Philosophy (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Botany Lecture (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Taxonomy and Ecology Lecture 27 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Taxonomy and Ecology Lecture 26 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Clausen History (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Conceptions (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Specimen Sources (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Short Articles (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Cytology (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Crassulaceae (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Crassulaceae - Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Crassulaceae - Cytology (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Oakley Corners (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Chemung Co., NY (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Dryden Lake and Vicinity (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Lists for Trips - Junius (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Plants collected on Trips (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Collections of RTC (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Asteraceae (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Specimen Correspondence, 1938-80 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Villadia (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Handbook of Sedum (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Ophioglossaceae - correspondence (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Ophioglossaceae - Short Articles and Lectures (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Botrychium - correspondence (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Research: Mainly 1960s, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Project Summaries and Notes by Rick and Hynn Benjamin, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Botrychim Correspondence, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Ophioglossum vulgatum (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Dispersal of Plants (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Distribution of Specimens (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Exchanges of Specimens (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence on Exchanges (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Leaves (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1946-1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Succulents (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Taxonomy of plants, 1960s-1070s (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Polypodiaceae, 1943-1954 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Droseraceae, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Ericaceae, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Sedum (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Sedum Correspondence, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sedum Reviews, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sedum Grants, 1950s-1970s (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sedum glaucphyllum, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Library Committee, 1944-May 1948 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Library Committee, June 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Series X. Sedum
  - Photographs - Record (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Photography (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Photographs - Record (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Howard Lyon Photos (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Culture of Plants (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Reading (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Reprints (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Colleagues - A-Garg (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Colleagues - Gentry-Zimmerman (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Other Colleagues (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Research (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Soils (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Monocots (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Unpublished Names (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Tornadoes (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Index - Sedum (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Sedum - Publishing Material (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Species Notes (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - General (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - subgenus Rhododia (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Record of Experiments (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Collection Notes (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Sedum files with data sheets, photos, correspondence and field notes - also information about the greenhouses, 1940s-1970s (Box 18-19)
  - San Bernardino Mountains Trip, 1967 - General Notes, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Monanthoidea, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Orthosedum, 1940s to 1950s (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Orthosedum, 1950s (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Orthosedum, 1950s (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Pachysedum, 1940s to 1950s (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Rhodiola, 1950s (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Rhodiola, 1950s (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Rosularia, 1940s to 1950s (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Sedastrum, 1940s (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Sedum, 1940s (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Sedotypus, 1940s (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Handbook of Sedum, 1940s to 1950s (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Telephium, 1940s (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Telephium, 1940s (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Handbook of Sedum - Subgenus Telephium, 1940s (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Crassulaceae - Flower Specimens studied by Maynard W. Quimby, 1930s (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Crassulaceae - sedum (D-H) Index of Species and Subspecies, 1950s to 1960s (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Crassulaceae - sedum Subgenus Pachysedum, 1940s (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Sedum borschii, 1950s to 1970s (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Sedum gormania, 1940s to 1960s (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Sedum rosea, 1940s (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Sedum Subgenus - Fruiticisedum, 1940s to 1950s (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Manuscript of "Sedum of North America" Chapter V "Sampling Surveys", 1960s to 1970s (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Sedum fieldnotes in notebooks in Box #11
- Series XI. Plant Data
  - Fabaceae (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Leguminosae (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Leguminosae - Desmodium (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Leguminosae - Gleditsia (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Leguminosae - Gymnocladus (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Leguminosae - Pachyrrhizus (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Leguminosae - Phaseolus (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Leguminosae - Sesbania (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Leguminosae - Trifolium (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Fabaceae - Vicia (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fagaceae (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Gentianaceae (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Gentiana detronsa - North American subspecies (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Gentianaceae - Halenia (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Gentianaceae - Gentiana (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Gentianaceae - Other Genuses (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Gentianaceae - Swertia (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Krameriaceae (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Lamiaceae (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Nymphaeceae (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Oxalidaceae (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Piperaceae (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Podosemonoceae (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Polemoniaceae (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Portulaceae (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Ranunculaceae (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Rosaceae (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Rubiaceae (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Salicaceae (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Salicaceae - Salix (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Sapindaceae (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Saxifragaceae (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Scrophulariacea (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Solariaceae (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Thymeleaceae (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Ulmaceae (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Violaceae (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Agavaceae (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Amaryllidaceae (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Araceae (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Arecaceae (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Cyperaceae (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Cyperaceae - Carex (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Iridaceae (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Liliaceae (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Najas A (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Najas B (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Najas - Notes (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Najas - Morphology (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Orchidaceae (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Poaceae (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Potamogetonaceae (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous Families (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Leguminosae - Astragalus (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Astragalus candiensis (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bauhinia (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Leguminosae - Cassia (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Leguminosae - Cercis (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Leguminosae - Crotalaria (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Leguminosae (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Leguminosae - Lupinus (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Leguminosae - Medicago (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Leguminosae - Pachyrrhizus 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Leguminosae - Pachyrrhizus 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Leguminosae - Prosopis (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Leguminosae - Robinia (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Hamamelidaceae (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Magnoliaceae (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Papaveraceae (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Plantaginaceae (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Polygonaceae (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Primulaceae (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Vasophyta (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Pteridophyta (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Equisetales Equisetaceae (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Lycopodiinae (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Bio Sciences 371 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Selaginellaceae (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Ferns (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Ferns - Mexico (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Polypodiaceae - Dryopteris (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Vascular Plants - Evolution and Taxonomy (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Gymnosperms (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Pinaceal (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Picea (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Taxaceae (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Ephedraceae (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Angiospermae (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Angiospermopsida - systems of Classification (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Acer migrum (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Anacardiaceae (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Annonaceae (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Apiaceae (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Asclepias (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Asteraceae (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Asteraceae - Crepis (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Berberidaceae (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Boraginaceae (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Brassicaceae (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Cactaceae (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Caryophyllaceae (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Colastraceae (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Chenopodiaceae (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Convolvulaceae (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Cucurbitaceae (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - New York - Empetraceae (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Euphorbiaceae (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Fabaceae (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Areas (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Ophioglossaceae (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Sedum (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Trip, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Crassulaceae (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Mucizonia (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Sedum oreades (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Sedum malacophyllum (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Sedum hakonense (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Sedum epidendrum (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Sedum unicum (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Sedum stephani (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Villadia - Mexican Plateau (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Villadia misera (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Villadia jurgensenii (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Villadia batesii (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Pachyphytum (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Lenophyllum (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Series XII. Photos
  - Photos of Fingerlakes Region Plants (Box 17)
  - Photos of Sedum and various other (Box 20)